Guide to the Records of John Brademas Speeches 1965-1991 RG 3.0.10 RG 3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Getty Center for Education in the Arts National Conference, Los Angeles, CA, (The Arts & Their Teaching: Prospects & Problems), Feb 2, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Berlin/New York Essay, (Berlin/New York Project), Feb 3, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Press Conference, NYU, (Announcing New Drug & Alcohol Abuse Initiative), Feb 6, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Board of Trustees, Bobst, (Report to Executive Committee), Feb 6, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - McGeorge Bundy Book Reception, Bobst, (JB Remarks Honoring Bundy), Feb 6, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Student Loan Default Problems, NYU, (Observations on the Problems), Feb 8, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - University Senate, Bobst, (Report to University Senate), Feb 9, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Athenian Ball, Pierre Hotel, (JB Accepts Hellene of the Year Award), Feb 15, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - FAS Board of Overseers Meeting, NYU, (JB Informal Remarks), Feb 16, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Mid-Atlantic Club Luncheon, Regency Whist, (Education for a Strong & Secure America), Feb 16, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - JB FNN Interview, (Interview), Feb 22, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - President's Council reception, Western Pub. Co,.(JB Talking Points), Feb 22, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - The Challenge of International Education,NYU, (JB Essay for Journal of International Affairs), Feb 22, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - United Way/NYU Community Fund Campaign Reception, NYU, (JB Brief remarks), Feb 23, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Comptroller General Luncheon, NYU, (JB Remarks), Feb 27, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - NYU Day in Albany, Albany, NY, (JB Briefing & Talking Points), Feb 28, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Metro Center Benefit Luncheon, Waldorf-Astoria, (JB Remarks at 6th Annual Mtg.), Mar 1, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - NYC Partnership/Urban Research Center Breakfast, D'Agostino, (JB Talking Points), Mar 2, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Medical Center Board, Med. Ctr., (Report to the Full Board), Mar 2, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Afternoon at Washington Square, Bobst, Atrium, (JB Remarks to Top Undergrad Candidates), Mar 5, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, Bobst, (JB Informal Remarks), Mar 8, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - History Department's Ramasco Lecture, NYU, (JB Brief Welcome), Mar 9, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Aphrodisisas Colloquim, NYU, (JB Intro), Mar 9, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - University Senate, Bobst, (Report to University Senate), Mar 9, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Board of Trustees, 3rd Ave Dorm, (Report to the Full Board), Mar 13, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - 22nd Annual Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner, Waldorf-Astoria, (Dinner Honoring John Tischman), Mar 15, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon, NYU, (JB Remarks), Mar 23, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - 4th Annual Petrie Lecture in Entrepreneurship,Tisch Hall, (Petrie Lecture), Mar 28, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Association of American Publishers Annual Meeting, Boca Raton, FL, (JB Keynote Address), Mar 30, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Archbishop Lakovds Enthronement Luncheon, Waldorf-Astoria, (Libretto & Remarks Celebrating 30th Anniver. of the Enthronement), Apr 2, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Lee Hamilton Lecture & Dinner, Vanderbilt Hall, (JB Remarks), Apr 3, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Medical Center Board, NYU, (JB Report to Full Board), Apr 4, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - NYU Family Dinner, Harmonie Club, (JB Talking Points at Dinner Hosted by David Kriser), Apr 5, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Presidential Scholars Reception, Main Bldg., (Reception Honoring l0th Anniversary), Apr 8, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Annenberg Program Debate, NYU, (JB Political Debate), Apr 10, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Rudin Reception, NYU, (JB Remarks & Welcome), Apr 11, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - NYU Alumni Reception in Connecticut, Marriott, (JB Talking Points), Apr 12, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Reception Honoring Nigerian Novelist, Pres. Conf. Rm, (Reception for Chinua Achebe), Apr 13, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - University Senate, NYU, (JB Report to University Senate), Apr 13, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Books, Babies, and Libraries Conf., NY Public Lib,. (Books, Babies & Libraries: Making the Connection), Apr 13, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Religion & Public Policy Conference Panel, Georgetown Univ., (The Role of Religion in the Formation of Public Officials: Theoretical), Apr 14, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Northeastern Association of Graduate Schools, Albany, NY, (JB Remarks), Apr 14, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Law School Revue, School of Law, (JB "Phantom" Remarks), Apr 14, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, Coles, (JB Address), Apr 16, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Laudatio of the Honorable J. William Fulbright, Athens, Greece, (Athinai Prize), Apr 20, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Piece for Bing, NYU, (NYU Advances), Apr 21, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Subcommittee on Energy & Water Development of the Committee on Appropriations, Washington D.C., (JB Statement), Apr 21, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Subcommittee on Natural Resources Agriculture Research, & Environment of the Committee on Science, Space, and Technology, Wash, D.C., (JB Statement), Apr 21, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Conference on Abused Children, NY Acad. of Med., (JB Brief Welcome), Apr 27, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Reception Honoring E.L. Doctorow, Pres. Conf. Rm., (JB Talking Points), Apr 27, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - NYU Metropolitan Studies Conference on Children, Vanderbilt Hall, (JB Remarks for Conference), Apr 28, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching/American for Generational Equity Regional Conf., Univ. Theater, (The Generational Contract: Educating All Our Youngsters for the 1990's), Apr 28, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Washington Square Arch 100th Anniversary Celebration, Wash. Sq. Arch, (JB Remarks for Celebration), Apr 30, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Nexus Article, (Is the Agenda for Science Too Important To Be Left to Scientists?), May 1989 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Penthouse Dinner honoring Robert Maxwell, Penthouse, (JB Brief talking point), May 1, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Advances at NYU, NYU, May 2, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - CASH Luncheon, NYU, (JB Briefing), May 2, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - PBS "Author, Author" Taping Remarks, NYC, (Dean Harvey Stedman), May 2, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - SEHNAP Prism Award Luncheon, Windows on World, (Honoree: Robert Maxwell), May 3, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, Bobst-Snow, (JB Remarks at Reception & Dinner), May 3, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - University Senate, NYU, (JB Report to the Senate), May 4, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Greek Press of the Diaspora Dinner, D'Agostino Hall, (JB Brief Remarks), May 6, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Omni Desk Conference, NYU, (Some Social Implications of New Technologies), May 8, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Board of Trustees, Bobst, (JB Report), May 8, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - IFA Board Meeting, Bobst, (JB Report), May 11, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - 25-Year Service Awards, Bobst-Snow, (JB Talking Points), May 11, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Reception, Stern Home, (JB Remarks), May 11, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - NYU Community Fund, Bobst-Conf. Rm,.(Check Presentation Event), May 16, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner, Bobst-Snow, (JB Remarks), May 17, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Medical Center Commencement, Carnegie Hall, (Script for Med. Ctr. Exerc.), May 18, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Alumni Commencement Breakfast, Bobst, (JB Remarks), May 18, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Albert Gallatin Medalist, (Taggart Whipple), May 18, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Commencement 1989 Honorary Degree Citations, (Honorees: Harry Blackmun, Gertrude Elion, Severo Ochoa, Isaac Stern, John Johnson, Colin Powell, Pindaros Vagelos), May 18, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - 157th Commencement Exercises, Wash. Sq. Park, (Commencement Scripts), May 18, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - White Burkett Miller Center of Public Affairs, U. of VA, (Reflections on Congress), May 19, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Brasenose College Charitable Foundation Dinner, Penthouse, (Talking Points for Dinner), May 30, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Herbert R. Silverman Scholarship Fund Reception, Bobst, (JB Remarks), Jun 1, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Board of Trustees, Bobst, (JB Report to Exec.Committee), Jun 5, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - Medical Center Board, Med. Ctr,.(JB Report), Jun 6, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    3 1142 042254741
  - Wayne E. Hirschkorn Memorial Fund Reception, Bobst, (JB Remarks), Jun 6, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - Cultural & Educational Agreement between the USA & Spain, Washington, DC, (JB Remarks), Jun 7, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - Regency Breakfast Meeting of Gallatin Associates & President's Council, Regency Hotel, (JB Talking Points), Jun 7, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 119)
  - Archivists Round Table of Metropolitan New York,(JB Statement for Press Kit), Jun 13, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 120)
  - Message to NYU/Yugoslavia Marketing Seminar, Yugoslavia, (JB Brief Message), Jun 16, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 121)
  - Gannet Center Conference, Hotel Dorset, (Higher Education in the 90's: Prospects & Problems), Jun 18, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 122)
  - Medical Center Faculty meeting, Med. Ctr., (JB Remarks), Jun 19, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254709
  - Penthouse Dinner Honoring the Mayor of Barcelona (Pascual Maragall), Penthouse, (JB Talking Points), Jun 21, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Article Submitted for Oxford Today, (JB Remarks), Jun 23, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Silver Shalis cruise, Silver Shalis, (Hosted by: Larry & Klara Silverstein), Jun 28, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Nomination of Marian Wright Edelman for McGraw-Hill Prize, NYU, (Nomination for McGraw -Hill Prize), Jun 30, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - The Honorable Terry Sanford Letter, (Letter From JB: Agenda for Higher Education), Jul 5, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Response to Newsday Editorial on Forgiveness/Scholarship Payback, ( Reactions), Jul 6, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Funding for Fairness, (JB Remarks), Aug 2, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Introduction to Medical Center Brochure,(JB Statement), Aug 22, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Convocation, Loeb, (JB Remarks), Sep 5, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Mayoral Candidate Debates, Law School, (JB Remarks), Sep 6, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - JB Drug Op-Ed, (Drugs), Sep 6, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees, Med. Ctr., (JB Remarks to Exec.Committee), Sep 7, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Community Service Society Retired Senior Volunteer Program, Sheraton Centre, (JB Remarks), Sep 14, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Introduction of Senator Moynihan at NAICU Leadership Conference, NYU, (JB Introduction of Moynihan), Sep 14, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees/Exec. Comm., Bobst, (JB Remarks to Exec. Committee), Sep 18, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Caldwell College 50th Anniversary Convocation, Caldwell, NJ, (JB Remarks), Sep 20, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Covenant of Peace Award Dinner, Sheraton Centre, (JB Remarks), Sep 20, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Dedication of the Henry Viscardi High School, Albertson, NY, (JB Speech), Sep 21, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Hagop Kevorkian Center Cultural Heritage Conference, Law School, (JB Remarks), Sep 21, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - World Management Congress, NYU, (JB Briefing), Sep 21, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Georgetown Inaugural Luncheon, Georgetown Univ,.(Lunch Marking the Inauguration of the 47th President of Georgetown University), Sep 23, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - GPA Naming Press Conference (Wagner Press Conference), Bobst, (JB Remarks), Sep 25, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Memorial Service for Sidney Hook, Law School, (JB Remarks), Sep 25, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Tokyo Broadcasting System Luncheonm, Pres. Conf. Rm., (JB Remarks & Awarding of Presidential Citations to Donald Richie & Kozo Hamaguehi), Sep 26, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Relations Program Reception, Penthouse, (JB Talking Points), Sep 26, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - New Graduate Students Reception, Bobst, (JB Talking Points), Sep 27, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial lecture, Vanderbilt Hall, (JB Remarks at 8th Lecture), Sep 27, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - IRTF Benefit Dinner, Plaza Hotel, (Benefit Dinner w/Mssrs. Brinkley, Chancellor and Cronkite), Sep 28, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Luncheon for Spanish Minister Semprun, Bobst, (Lunch in Honor of Jorge Semprun), Sep 29, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Humanities Council Readings on Greenwich Village, Vanderbilt Hall, (JB Remarks), Oct 3, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - University Senate, NYU, (JB Report to the Senate), Oct 5, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Luce Professorship Inaugural Lecture, D'Agostino Hall, (JB Remarks), Oct 5, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Visit by President (Vassiliou) of Cyprus, Bobst/Tisch, (JB Briefing Points at Round Table-Discussions, Remarks at Hellenic Studies Lecture, & Talking Points at Penthouse Dinner), Oct 5, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Medical Center Board, Med. Ctr., (JB Report to the board), Oct 10, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - UAA Presidents' Press Reception & Dinner, Bobst, (JB Remarks), Oct 11, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, Heights Lounge, (JB Talking Points), Oct 11, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - New Jersey Regional Alumni Reception/Distinguished Alumni Awards Presentation, Short Hills, NJ, (JB Talking Points), Oct 12, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Board of Trustees, Bobst, (JB Report to Full Board), Oct 16, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Luncheon Honoring Soviet Filmmakers, Bobst, (JB Talking Points), Oct 17, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Reception to Inaugurate the Arthur Imperatore Professorship, Tisch Hall, (JB Talking Points at Recep. Installing Lawrence White), Oct 30, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Real Estate Institute (REI) Campaign Announcement, Midtown Center, (JB Remarks), Oct 31, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Penthouse Dinner for Senator Ralph Marino, Penthouse, (JB Talking Points), Oct 31, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Lecture to Celebrate the Nancy Hanks Endowment at Duke University, Duke Univ., (The Arts & Politics:Rethinking the American Commitment to Culture), Nov 2, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Temple Emanu-El Forum, 5th Avenue, (JB Speech), Nov 5, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Donald MacNaughton Symposium/John Palmer-Dean of the Maxwell School, Syracuse Univ., (Preparing for the 21st Century: Perspectives on Public Service,Governance & Global Realities), Nov 8, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - All-University Dinner Dance, Coles, (JB Talking Points), Nov 8, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Senate Report, NYU, (JB Report), Nov 9, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Dedication of the Elmer Holmes Bobst Memorial Room/Bobst Award Dinner, Bobst, (JB Remarks), Nov 9, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - United Hellenic American Congress Dinner Dance, Chicago Hilton, (JB Remarks), Nov 11, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Dedication of Onassis Center, Onassis Center, (JB Remarks), Nov 13, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Trustees Scholars Reception, Bobst, (JB Remarks), Nov 15, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - CLACS Luncheon, Bobst, (JB Talking Points), Nov 16, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Dinner in Honor of Mayor Wagner, Bobst, (JB MC), Nov 16, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - "In Praise of Libraries.. ." Luncheon, Bobst, (Lunch Honoring Marie Schwartz & Welcoming Fr. Tim Healy), Nov 17, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Scholarship Foundation of St. Joseph County, South Bend, IN, (JB Speech), Nov 19, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Lecture of Jose Maria Maravall, Main Bldg., (Lecture Commemorating the Juan Carlos Chair), Nov 20, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Washington Square Park Gift Acknowledgement, Wash. Sq. Park, (JB Talking Points), Nov 21, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - 59th Annual Mtg. of Middle States Assoc. of Collegiate Registrars, Atlantic City, (JB Speech), Nov 27, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Annual Management Conference at the General Accounting Office (GAO), Chantilly, VA, (Rebuilding the Public Service), Nov 29, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Medical Center Board, NYU, (JB Report), Dec 5, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Elie Wiesel Lecture & Dinner, Eisner & Lubin, (JB Remarks), Dec 6, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Senate Report, NYU, (JB Report), Dec 7, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Dr. Howard A. Rusk Memorial Service, Farkas Audit., (JB Remarks), Dec 7, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Ed Koch Reception, Commons Room, (JB Talking Points to Welcome Disting. Visiting Marnold Fellow, Ed Koch), Dec 11, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Board of Trustees, NYU, (JB Report), Dec 11, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Education Week Interview, (JB Briefing), Dec 15, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon, NYU, (JB Report), Dec 14, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - SEHANP Faculty Meeting, NYU, (JB Remarks), Dec 18, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Carnegie Council Breakfast, 64th Street, (JB Remarks), Dec 19, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - A Tribute to Arthur Lehning, NYU, Dec 1989 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Message from the President, NYU, (JB Message in Staff Handbook), Jan 1990 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - LPB Medical Center Board, Medical Center, (JB Report), Jan 9, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - MAT Dinner for Lord and Lady Briggs, Penthouse, (Informal Dinner to Welcome Lord and Lady Briggs), Jan 5, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - LPB Members of the NY Regional Office of GAO, World Trade Ctr,. ("Rebuilding the Public Service"), Jan 17, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - LPB Community Service/Youth Service Dinner, NYU, (JB talking points), Jan 18, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - JG Texaco Roundtable Luncheon, Texaco Headqtrs., ("Challenge for the 1990s: Reforming America's Public Schools"), Jan 18, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - LPB USA TODAY Luncheon, Gannett Headqtrs., (JB remarks honoring the All-USA College Academic Team), Jan 19, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - MAT New York/Italy Medical Symposium ("Due Case, Una Tradizione"), Grand Hyatt, (JB remarks at second annual Symposium), Jan 20, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - KF Global Affairs Institute Speech, Tuscanny Hotel, (JB keynote address- discussing global trends in business), Jan 21, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - JG CASE Middle Atlantic District II, Waldorf-Astoria, ("Why Support Higher Education: Making Our Case In the 1990s"), Jan 22, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - MAT Faculty Resource Network Luncheon, Bobst, Ben Snow, (JB remarks), Jan 25, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - LPB IFA Board Meeting, Inst. of Fine Art, (JB report), Jan 31, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - LPB Florida Alumni Reception, Boca Raton, FL, (JB remarks), Feb 1, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - LPB REI Penthouse Dinner, Penthouse, (JB remarks on campaign for REI Master's Program and McGhee medal presentation to Klara Silverstein), Feb 6, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - LPB Senate Report, Ben Snow, (JB report), Feb 8, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - KF Celia Farris Dinner, Palm Beach, FL, ("An Evening in Celebration of American Musical Theatre"), Feb 10, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - LPB Response to University of Oklahoma Press, (International Education), Feb 15, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - KF Chicago Alumni Reception, Chicago, IL, (JB remarks), Feb 18, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 89)
  - LPB Urban Research Center Lunch, NYU, ("Media and Local Politics"), Feb 20, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - LPB Press Conference Announcing the Grantees of the RWJ Foundation's "Fighting Back" Program, Washington, DC, (JB statement at press conf.), Feb 21, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 91)
  - LPB Messages for "Benefactors" Book, (Tribute to benefactors of NYU), Feb 21, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 92)
  - KF Riklis Ackerman Dinner, Ackerman Home, (JB accepts $10 million gift from Riklis family for biomedical research), Feb 22, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - JG & LPB Op-ed for The Chronicle, (Continuing Education), Feb 23, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - KF NYU in Albany Day, Albany, NY, (JB remarks at luncheon for Wagner School alumni, address to NYU delegation, and closing remarks at reception), Feb 27, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - JG SEHNAP Reception for Chancellor Joseph Fernandez and Penthouse Dinner, Ben Snow, (JB talking points), Feb 28, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 96)
  - KF Metro Center Benefit Luncheon, Waldorf-Astoria, (JB remarks at seventh annual luncheon/Arthur Sulzberger presented with the Torch of Learning Award), Mar 1, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - LPB White Burkett Miller Center Transcript, ("The Congress and the Presidency"), Mar 1, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 98)
  - JG Annual Archons Banquet, Marriot Marquis, (JB receives the Athenagoras Human Rights Award), Mar 3, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 99)
  - LPB Sunday at the Square, Bobst, (JB remarks), Mar 4, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 100)
  - JG National Institute of Social Sciences New York Issues Luncheon, Harvard Square, (JB Remarks), Mar 5, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 101)
  - LPB Medical Center Board of Trustees, Med. Science Bldg, (JB remarks to Exec. Comm.), Mar 6, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 102)
  - LPB United Way/NYU Community Fund Campaign Reception, NYU, (JB brief remarks), Mar 7, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - KF Andreotti Convocation, Vanderbilt Hall, (JB remarks at special academic celebration in honor of Prime Minister of the Rep. of Italy), Mar 8, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - LPB Senate Report, Medical Center, (JB report), Mar 8, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - LPB Hagop Kevorkian Center Lunch, D'Agostino Hall, (JB remarks at lunch), Mar 9, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 106)
  - LPB Presentation of John Jay Award to McGeorge Bundy/Intro of Sen. Moynihanat cIcu Annual Meeting, Albany, NY, (JB remarks), Mar 12, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 107)
  - LPB Guggenheim Recommendation for Mark Derr, NYU, (JB recommendation), Mar 13, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 108)
  - KF Charles Waldo Haskins Award Dinner, The Pierre, (JB remarks), Mar 13, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 109)
  - LPB Ditchley Foundation Conference, Univ. of Texas, (JB remarks on Political Leadership), Mar 16, 1990-Mar 17, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - KF Conference on Czech Literature and Culture, Loeb, (JB remarks), Mar 19, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - LPB Luncheon for Ambassador Santamaria, Bobst, (JB remarks at lunch), Mar 19, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - LPB Board of Trustees, Bobst, (JB report), Mar 19, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - KF Sussmuth Lecture and Dinner, Bobst, (JB remarks), Mar 19, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - LPB Conference on US-USSR Cooperation at the UN, D'Agostino Hall, (JB remarks), Mar 20, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - JG Luncheon for Sir Raymond Hoffenberg, Bobst, (JB talking points), Mar 21, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - KF Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner, Waldorf-Astoria, (JB remarks and presentation of award to Brian Strum), Mar 21, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - LPB Faculty Council Luncheon, Bobst, (JB talking points), Mar 22, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - JG NYU Family Dinner (David Kriser), Harmonie Club, (JB talking points at dinner for NYU Trustees, Dean, Faculty & Admin. (hosted by David Kriser), Mar 22, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - JG Induction as Honorary Member of the Inst. of International- Public Law & International Relations, Greece, (JB speech at the University of Thessaloniki), Mar 28, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - JG Speech to Propeller Club & Association of Friends of Anatolia, Greece, (JB remarks at AnatoliaCollege on international education, Greek studies, and the Onassis Center), Mar 29, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 121)